We have a call to the Board of Regorations.
Monkeys and Gaffle.
We are the Monday of May 3.
We are going to do a cruise line.
Thank you for the question.
These have five.
No problem.
Five.
Three.
A group of minutes.
The day for my feet.
Twenty, twenty, one.
Big number twenty, six.
Twenty, one.
And they were 28.
Two.
Twelve.
One.
Second.
He says Five.
No book.
Five.
One.
Four.
Five.
The time we put in is all wrong here and you spend on it with your friend family and friends.
Other things that you might want to do, just spend time here for our own family and family.
You kind of mean things better than it.
Appreciate it.
The ride is wrong here.
And don't end it.
Do it again.
Thank you.
We got a little.
We're going for a ride.
But we don't think we're going to do it.
Let's then present the ride or hit a appreciation recognition for your lead.
But then you can't say anything.
That's just because there's going to be a huge point.
It's going to be a huge point.
That's going to be a huge point.
If you're going to do it,
what do you think.
I think that's going to be a great point,
I agree.
Okay?
Give someone some respect or bread.
that I was a fourth obeyed in the medical institution of the United States, and the
constitution of the State of Oklahoma, and then I will not know if we've received
directly or indirectly, and any many more other valuable things, for the performance, for
the performance, and any after-duty pertainence, my office, other than the compensation
allowed by law, I further sperm, that I would make this charge, according to the best
of my ability, for the best of my ability, the duties as my office during such time,
as I am a member of the Miami City Council, and the Board of Trustees, and the Board of Trustees
of the Miami City Council, and the Board of Trustees, of the Miami City Council, as the city
in the United States, and the constitution of the state of Oklahoma, and then I will not know
We follow in ways where it refers to someone's word or word that I support obeyed and the Constitution.
That I support obeyed and the Constitution.
At the end of the day.
At the Constitution.
At the state of Oklahoma.
And then I will love knowing you received directly your Avery briefly.
And I know I believe you're gay.
Any money or other valuable things?
For the performance, we're not performance.
For the performance, we're not.
Any actor duty?
For teenagers, my office.
Thank you, my office.
Other than the compensation, a lot, I wrote.
Other than the compensation, I wrote.
I further square our firm.
A worker's work or firm?
That I was a pretty good charge.
A employee's job.
According to the best of my abilities.
The duties of my office.
Through a such time as I am a member of the Mining City Council.
Through a set of times, I am a member of a time as the court.
The court for warful.
And the board of trustees of the Mining City Council.
Of the city of Mining City Council.
The city of Mining City Council.
Praise me, James.
I'm the president.
My name is Mining City, but I'm the Chair?
The Secretary for Education.
Thanks.
So what?
He said,
Submerge.
He said.
The rage.
There's always a point that makes deserve a special amount of down-down
Rebellion that we can be.
Are they?
Submerge.
He said,
All right.
Well, the thing that was good, the first of the cases, we have one of the night.
Which is the job that we need to pay.
Yeah.
That's a very good statement.
And I had to kind of select a few things to comment which would be.
So, it's, um, a sharp find.
I have to find some things at the center of check.
But everything is in the action.
What the function associates.
We have to use the drug.
It's a lawsuit, so that the form of the supply and add to your other reports.
That's an important information for you.
We can't question three upon that before you go to sign.
Back to the design.
Resuming those two have been down to producing out the subject outside of the city for anything else
online, should be considered and choosing all of them.
If I'm a people of things, I'm going to be a question.
This is the right way to plan.
On February 4, 2019, Sean and City Commission have been able
to the City Manager at Brewer on $70,000
for sure, for sure, for sure, for sure, for sure,
for sure, for sure.
Our original socials have been clean and affordable
out of three years.
On the June 5th of 2021, the A.A.
Alpharo District will need all of their product into $7,000 dollars.
They asked Jim Denham, Arnold and Associates
that the product that they have supported them
and have agreed to share the A.A.A.
to reveal the misuse of restricted funds.
Arnold and Associates chose not to answer the question.
On two ways in their 20-hour and social supply
telephone, state council results,
it's a best way to find it, and on April 1, 2020,
telephone, ring a higher Arnold and Socialist
to be known as Friends of God.
Some of us all love it, it's not clear you're honest
on it, but friends of God, the wood, and the suitors
to find unique designs, and their products,
have pushed other citizens to have a friends of God,
and need an agarosis of its deducted or implemented to be followed.
As a citizen of the IAR, we are encouraging you to do
to receive all of your opinions, please take a close
to the big health and come to the final statement.
Thank you, Josh.
In the case of your consent agenda,
instead of that, we're going to be a true one
to love a new book, P.E.
I'm looking forward to your vote.
So please have a couple.
How cool.
On her David?
Hi.
15 Executive Regents.
Sorry for the excellent comments.
Another day for a college and so here for this week, you're only going on.
Hi.
And this is the digitized EGC.
Every year we bring one before we cancel every year.
Another dimension to the other services,
I should murder her in, but go to him.
So, by say, statute, cancel means required to call or order
on it, and murdering it is the end of the fiscal year,
which is why you see this about this time of year.
The audit is a financial statements,
and that means that at well the handling of it is actually
what records say isn't that.
A little bit about the process.
So, we send that a request to work because we don't hear that a lot.
I know the push on what it would be.
We send one out to twenty-one respondents,
and put it on our website on February 5th, with a delay of March 1st.
We didn't see two proposals.
In that proposal.
or in our RFP, there is actually a checklist that, of that cell,
you would respond to, however, when it arrived.
When we received those proposals, the Missile wanted to enter
myself separately.
We scored each one using that checklist.
And then in a later day, the person agent calls me,
and she tells the American College of American Sports.
We do not know about the price of this and this,
because of that comes in the field of blood.
So at the same meeting, after she tells the American
scores, she opened the seal of the formula,
and one of the questions that we can't answer to the seal,
the seal of blood is,
that the formula was being in the wrong way to take
and what it cost for an office, actually,
and how long has it taken.
So here are the scores, but all of this is in the pattern,
it's now referred to as actually the pattern.
The scores of the American score were for artists,
101, HSPG and socials, that was the other one.
There was 101, too.
They both got a score of 10,
what we call the timing score,
which is that's the one that people understood,
and what's the pricing.
So, Arnold had a total score of 200 and 11,
and HSPG got a score of 202.
And in the table below, it showed us the cost estimates
that we've been seeing what actors score, and it was there.
So, couple things to note,
Arnold's such a pass then,
the last five artists for the city.
The first four of those five artists was then
by Arnold and Paul, he had a smooth HSPG.
HSPG did not have a government argument,
but it was in the waiting room there.
Great back.
I don't say the name of his HSPG.
We really seriously consider changing files every time.
This is the fourth time that I've been involved in
finance that we have on HSPG.
And it's important that we have new eyes
looking at our documents when this comes up.
So, one of the things with,
so, Arnold's score of highest,
and you know, we've got two responses.
But the biggest thing is now a new team
is actually looking at our records.
And there are a few different questions,
and that's a very different thing.
They asked for one of the documents.
And again, they're really looking to see
what's in the mind,
who's what our record says,
and what a financial statement is.
Some other things to note,
Arnold's best had,
they have decades of experience
in a municipal building.
They had very different answers.
They've done lots for the upcoming municipal buildings.
Municipally, but also known as OMA,
the ODPRB, which is the Oklahoma water resources
before they've done bodies for the state of the home
of the department's securities and insurance department.
And then what we're really looking for is a lot.
experience in the municipal auditorium, and they've done
scans of that, a book error, and then, or it's also
a book of access to some of the cities that they've recorded.
I would like to bring you the moment, if you represent,
are there's just an answer in the questions you might have?
I'd like to ask you to be able to talk to me about the last
40 years of the art of the living, and have been talking
in the States later today, right?
No.
Carvering sessions, because actually, you're just a car room
on the administrative side to use Carvering sessions as a consultant,
and they help us prepare our financial statements.
That's really when things are happening in a family life,
which will be a reference in creating a financial statements,
to prevent the other, and then that will be a problem.
I'm going to give you a little piece of the amount of the garbage
we're already getting, so it's, and I just,
come here to be a good night to answer any questions
you would like to be an answer at the work,
any issues you would like for me to address, and I think of you that.
You, you're at your public office, all you have to give you the address,
and you have that.
I can hand encourage you to call simply a term that the mayor,
the city of California, but they are ongoing client,
and I believe you will find very good references for us
with the city of California.
Say, Mr. President Shaw, you may continue to be a comment.
We're going to the mayor there and we're going to continue to be a vote.
I think we'll chance to ask him to sit in an afternoon,
so we'll be happy to see both of you.
Mr. Shaw, can you speak on the,
a common, kind of, and we can't.
I can want to speak to that case, specifically, that is,
in the, in the, in the, in the, in the real matter of four days to speak to it,
where it entrances to the line together for just barely a month,
coupled in their ends of that agreement, but it tends to be to be in general.
We do a lot of their financial statements, and the purpose of that,
is to apply it on whether or not they are presented in the tour,
the tour of the contract under government of high standards.
We're not engaged, are you, to, if you want to put on that.
It's a separate case, but I think we want those to be held up.
It's correct.
We can't do that work, but that's not what you are hiring in high-ranking.
Okay, so you're hiring us to a prime, confident state that's going to not.
They're presented in the warm days with different ways that put it down in the process,
which, for you, is the, I don't know what you're going to say.
And in doing that, we do cooperation to our transformations.
We do to test work.
But it is not at the level of order of death that we need.
be done to give you an opinion on whether or not there was any problem in the city.
So that is the level of work we need to do, or that we do too with this type of engagement.
Now, what I was trying to think about that situation, the partner that was in charge of the audit
that resulted in the loss of this and all over the firm, so that it's awesome when they would have
been on their audit.
In some of the four, yes, how does this happen when I see a firm based student?
The first one was, say, we've been in business school for 37 years now.
We have had one, lost one.
That is a very, very small number in the business category.
And I hope you understand that anyone can sue anyone, and that's not lost since work.
But no, it's not what happens when we see a firm as a student.
We have professional liability insurance, and actually we have a core bank.
And it's your fault.
The insurance company spends the end to resolve that.
Our insurance company dealt with the fact that situation and their attorneys manage that situation.
We don't hire attorneys.
We don't speak to the people still in us.
None of those days happen.
So, how does it get selling like a core?
Well, when the insurance companies, attorneys, believe that their cheapest course of it,
of action is to sell it out of court because of the cost of going to court is very expensive.
The insurance company does a power to raise out of Oklahoma.
So, all of those are very expensive costs for them.
Then they sell it when they believe they should sell it.
And so, we're not actually controlling that on our bank accounts.
If that kind of option is to share the power of these networks.
Anything else?
I think they should be very determined.
We're all out of the back there of the design and order for me to think of it.
That's the reason why I work for our examination.
Those two terms are interchangeable.
I think we'll turn with our examination of the State of California.
Those are the reasons.
Those are the reasons that normally said that when you already have an inkling of what we're concerned about.
In other words, it would be very expensive for the higher someone to do a broad base of all activities.
To try to see if there's any problem and you don't have the idea for that might be right.
The city is willing to want to pay for that.
So, what happens most often is we don't have to concern this person.
Or we have to concern with these accounts or these types of things.
transactions and then we came in a very narrow focus of we are working at this because it does take quite
pricey for clients. So what can you talk about as far as about a client who's been seeing
money all over the last several years and all over the country's other business.
I'm sorry again, it's probably stopped. So I don't have anything to go with background and I don't
a new partner for the city of Miami. I just picked it up. I don't know, maybe here now.
So I can tell you one of my needs for the most recent year. The years before that the partner in charge
is actually now including over the HSPG. So he's over there, noticing why you're on it. He will be a biologist in charge of it
for the poor previous year.
Finding the efficiencies of shortcomings in some way or another way.
Right. It can run the gamut of non-confinanced mistake law, non-confinanced.
Federal law, things not recorded correctly, I mean actually. First of all, they did a lot of work
about things like accounts not being right in style of timely. Those sorts of things.
Again, we don't apply on any of those. So just to know the difference between what are we saying
or confident of? We're saying we're confident that the financial statements are presented in accordance with
general accepted circumstances. We give you a report on compliance and Trump controls.
But that's the report based on what we saw while we were getting together in it.
So it's not an engagement to do that report, so much as that report is a byproduct of the work we did to get to the opinion.
The other question is, certainly. The issues that were brought to a council night in March,
were certainly something that we took into consideration, obviously, of course we would.
So we had the need to reach out to firm and ask them for their response to the issues
that were brought up to the council and we had a similar conversation to the information that we're not sharing
a few days. In addition to that, I myself reached out to the University of Oklahoma Council
right. I explicitly brought up the opportunity to succeed in going to their feedback
or matter. He's saying to the right guy, I think that's very right in the works for all
opportunities. So, she's thought that you're extremely right to confirm, you know, I think
his comments were something around the parents who were the best around you, and you're
very, very sensitive. Keeping in mind, but that is the announcing board's mission, is to
safeguard the public by assessing the qualifications of the parents in the safe and the
parents in the safe. And so, he's trying to figure out how he's doing to make sure that
something that they look into, and thought that in research and make sure that there's
anything to bring up the mission. Certainly, as they are, we're sort of fine. The C today is our
shape. Obviously, we're going to make sure that we haven't, we're just qualified to
record the CBA tracks. Anyway, that conversation, the conversation that I had, the reception
he had. In fact, I believe, you know, our purchasing process that we went through was extremely
consistent, fair, and accurate. As Jill did point out, we said, how to work in training,
herbs, and that back to herbs that we're actually working with in the city. We evaluate those
very closely. We make very close attention to what exactly there's the herb of the working
with the little cities contract. Because it's just stated, we do understand it since it's important.
We can't even survive. It's often possible because often that's better things are caught
that's saved out. And although it's not their core mission, the kind of way you're going to
say it's to try to go after a bit of a front front, they actually would be from my training
to be sure it's my kind of training to take home. They're always looking for a result.
Anything they find or see that the books, honest, they can point out. They make sure that
you're keeping it during the suicide has not to be divided like that. And if they see significant
risks, they can't do their own for a result to be inspired from passion and thought. So that would kind
of be a case that we did today, and keep it running, that we have to in a bit of honor to see
what it's worth. And specifically, Crawford and Associates, which should be regular
multiple, some of the lack of this is what we can say in the huge very regular term.
That is because our chemistry is also about all of the Associates. He's doing a bit of terms,
or essentially, you know, key.
in 19 modernized working on them, they have relax and say everything that each one of them
is doing in another performing the audience in North Korea or sitting back and sitting
back and sitting.
So it's not like we even have all of our kids in the NASA, the risk of the safety is very
lovely.
Now there's always group for error.
We don't need money, it's always, you know, in this case, they are dealing with the
looking to be inferred as you'll say that the money that we've worked with the money to
actually exist.
It's actually a different thing.
But the main report is as a new state of the United States, right?
They are not going in back trying to do this in North Korea, but they're going out of the
documents, they're making sure that the documents exist as the documents are being controlled
and they may actually be put in the front of them and they're following the gas and say it.
That means that if they say nothing, they will report to us immediately, these types of audits should
be found.
That's why they're not going to be the sex activities, it's something we have to do.
This is how we've listened to these audits themselves and make sure they're going to be working
public.
But our financial audits, or our own financial framework, take this, or act, we continue to go through
this process every few years, so we'll put it out for the more of them being.
As we get the share, you know, at this point, we're looking to be getting the data.
It's awesome, since we've had to participate in a nice, very basic and useful year.
That means then, you know, that is about a free-workable process that we've been doing previously.
If the camera's on the floor too, we're going to go back on the bed and see if we're going to
winters.
And then, we're going to take this time to be different results and we've got the ability
to be in the process that create the results of a massive failure and thank you for generating
a few different results.
So, to make myself and make some of the results, we're confident in the research and how we shall
do.
There's a scope of it that they may very go to the comments, and that being said, I have a
new problem with the recognition that you can't tell.
But when you said, Dr. Nancy Ward, did you ask that you specifically about what we're going to be?
I mean, they were absolutely aware that they've been able to talk to the doctor that they've had
an old race and a research at the time of the year, and had no wishes with what they
think they saw.
I think in this words, the fact that we have, for instance, year of veterans in the government
in the county, that's only at one.
The issue of things, it's pretty much made to itself.
We have that issue of Luxembourg.
In the courts, we were insurance.
We really have been very, very comfortable.
It's from the older.
Look at that.
One thing I might address the situation of being asked about the situation
and the farm decline to respond.
That was the response from the media.
And we do not respond to the media.
We work in the city council.
We respond to the city council.
And so, we will always respond to you.
You're very personal here in writing, whatever she requests of us,
but we do not respond to the media.
We're making a proposal.
7, we'll reject.
We'll accept it.
May this.
These have.
I've heard.
You know.
Double.
Harder.
5.
6.
Because it's a minute.
Which is the reasons the most of us did.
7.
8.
Where?
For council.
We need to announce.
About a few years.
How was on here?
So we can get something to make sure.
I think that.
Who?
It was a.
Back through on Friday night.
It was nice to.
Playing.
I said.
I.
I wrote this.
And then I did.
I.
It.
But.
So I think this was.
Back this week.
The.
It can.
We.
Let's not the.
No.
But I'll write it.
Mmm.
Oh, good.
That.
17.
Good.
A.
Oh.
Get the.
Have.
They're good.
They're bad to send me good.
But, how's that happen to the else in the else building?
I do.
In the man's world, Chuck finally makes us able to open the softball turn.
And it wasn't huge, but it was successful.
I was out there to kind of get playin' in.
And, so I'll coach it, reaching out to Chuck for how it was being run.
And they can carry out the new softball turn.
And then, on the side note of Thursday night, 38 teams, just over 400 young ladies from age,
four to 14 is, will be out there four times a week.
On the Tuesday Thursday, it's Friday.
And it will be the chaos.
I'm saying that out loud, I'm hearing it, because I'm thinking of stuff like that.
And it's going to, I can't get out of it.
And that's a on purpose.
It's our really focused care about the softball.
They should shut the bank attention, because this guy's done that to the seat.
And I'm going to see it through them on that.
So, I'm laying down to my, I think I could put it down on.
Because I was about to get there.
There's a bunch of girls who love that thing.
I'm inviting anybody, everybody.
They don't sit back.
They've wanders.
The impact of the sports to drive by out there.
Six, seven, a clock, Monday, 30th of Friday evening.
And seated.
And I'm getting back.
It's incredible.
How much does it go?
It's a long, some grand balls.
And grand ones.
Spend it to go.
What suits you.
Get a base hit.
So, that's all.
I want to add that.
But this team, when you think of these teams.
He thinks too.
And see.
We have people from here.
You live in a tax.
It's great to have also.
Show me.
You're all over.
And we talk to those folks.
They talk about the term.
It's a big region.
And the people they bring you.
And the impact of that.
And it's happening there.
And it's happening back there.
They came here.
And the impact here.
Our restaurants still.
A couple of separate restaurants.
They're protecting those journalists.
And they're smart.
They're protecting those.
They're working on that.
They're not a dozen.
They're helping them.
They're protecting those.
They're jam-packed.
And.
What this lady, her team do.
We've got to do behind them.
But there's no way that you take them on me.
They're getting back here.
And the only place we see is that there's a cash register.
For the fact.
And we need to get behind her and give her the tools.
The truck to them.
I mean, we keep bringing those guys out.
They're going to make it clear.
We were all standing.
All right, so go to the book of my team, send me a hand to this invitation.
Well I got a few things to share with you tonight, the great act of this.
We had a lot of the week in the early birthday of the last time.
That was in very, very busy last week.
Trying to get everything done.
I'm going to put the crew tonight.
Very excited.
We were going to go off the beat.
constantly doing the raising up, pulling them down together, and getting the benefits of all.
The acts of takeover on the end of the food trucks they had, to the food room, and to the
grocery, and to the slices of the food trucks. That's a good problem I have. So hopefully
you can be heard from some of those, the bits that we have with that community on the end of
your mind, or a bigger bit, and hopefully make a submission of their cruising life, which
they pass it on your mission last year. I think you're retired. Waiting for that night for
a long time. So I'm glad that I was in the rendition of it. I'll take it in the end, and
have to see if she damn family is very busy, because I thought it's a car that's probably very
busy, but I think it brought me a lot of the lots and lots of factors in the body.
I thought it was not going to happen. I thought it was a part of that, and I think it's going to be
a bit complicated because she'll be trying to dislocate it. So we had quite a part of the fact that
the last of two years that his life has a life with building a new 76-prior of two older machines
in the course of discipline. We're out of the complexity of the three-wheel, but it was great
to eye all the down in the windshield. Luckily it looked like there was no one intended to do
the performance of the make-tree. We could say she was out there in the business and in the
department. We could say we could just be in the scenes like. I'm sorry.
Same thing as neat dogs. These scenes back to make it look like that's correct. Anyway,
great men. It was so thorough to be able to get to that point. You know, speaking here with the other
great things, we've got kind of obviously raw, actually way to be able to be able to be more cool.
Something really made cool, simply. This week we're working on the people.
Hope that that ramp up into this month that we can start with a lighter.
We can be lighter and solved, so we're obviously still in a month's show in a second months away.
and we had a bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit because every time you raise it, it would be tough.
The way you're trying to make it to the end.
So whether obviously this takes a very good lead to that time limit,
but we have started producing all the paperwork that hired your temporary staff,
so that all of our folks' ways can work with concessions,
and my guard and all the things that we in place to talk with that.
I'm maybe more interested to talk about it.
You know, the banking is a big deal.
It's a big deal.
They're going to start memorizing this week, so they can get open.
Hope we can have everything in place.
And we're going to have a little bit of something to do.
So this is going to get out there and start doing that.
We're going to have a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of that.
I'm going to be the last thing that I wanted to mention was just tonight,
because we're going to have a great experience of watching this in a time of work.
We've got great folks who basically needed to care for this week.
We've got a lot of work to do.
So, I think that's going to be a great deal.
We've got great folks who basically needed to care to leave this community.
And we're willing to stay on a great, great work in science,
to the scouts of the decision.
And, you know, the things that I've never talked about are extremely good.
You can use your things.
The issues that Mr. Bowley brought up tonight.
We're always concerned to be missed out.
In fact, they're terrible.
Because those are the works of the works that he was going to never want to find out.
That the money was being misproperated in this evening.
The works that he gave me.
These are not our bonds.
This is not our money.
He's hiding in my neighborhood.
That's gave me a note.
We're going to be staying on a great state note.
And he says, it's too hard to buy something.
I'm sure he'll be processes.
I answer that as always.
It should be hard.
It should be very hard.
Because you're spending something else to come.
And so, the fact that we never look side to the fact that we are entrusted with the energy.
The government and the money's going to take to the edge of the run.
And say, this is not our money.
It should be difficult to stay.
It should always be hard.
So, I would like to think we'll be able to take those things.
We're trying to be important.
Then we are a village.
We're going to be very happy to be here today.
So, as a group, a guy who can make decisions as a group.
You know tonight, you can blame both, no, it's the eyes of the intervention.
That's the way it should work in the work of the way it should.
Because it's willing to both, and it's the work of the, after most of the other people,
it was only to stand up and not come to you with that.
And you need right there, like, around that, and it will never be shocked
and then everyone will be shocked with the outcome of the vote.
And never if we can go with the votes in the week or into it,
and it's never even matter at certain points that should simply process it.
That means that the Black Sea, the advocacy, the advocacy, the advocacy of the individuals,
the support of the city, and the impact of the year and health of the community.
And I can't, I always want to mention what I'm providing you with all the information you need.
Well, if I'm not, at least I have to push it to the area and if there is a solution to turning your own lives,
you will be able to add the satisfaction that you should make sure you have it.
Thank you for all the free time and participation that you've put it out, but you may leave me a lot.